

### **PROFILE:**

Information Communications
Technology Expert skilled in
Computer Networking, Databases,
Java, SQL, Microsoft Excel,
Customer Service, and Computer
Literacy.

Dependable ICT Tech with excellent software, hardware and operations knowledge.

Strong technical expertise combined with analytical approach and performance-oriented mindset.

Strong education professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Masinde Muliro University of Science and Technology.

#### **CONTACTS:**

PHONE: +254711497488

in WEBSITE:

linkedin.com/in/washingtone-aura-0109131b6

**EMAIL**:

aurawashingtone@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES:**

- Sports Football
- News
- Research

# **COMMUNICATION:**

- Linguistics speaks confidently in English and Swahili
- Good PowerPoint presentations

# WASHINGTONE AURA

# Computer Scientist

#### **EDUCATION**

#### MASINDE MULIRO UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Kakamega, Kenya Sep 2015 - Dec 2019 Bachelor's degree, Computer Science First Class Honors

#### NAMASOLI SECONDARY SCHOOL

Kakamega, Kenya Jan 2011 - Nov 2014 Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education Grade A-

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **KCA UNIVERSITY**

Nairobi, Kenya Distance Learning Support - Intern May 2022 - Aug 2022

#### **MUDASA ACADEMY**

Vihiga; Kisumu, Kenya Information Communication Technology Teacher Information Communication Technology Support Jan 2020 – Apr 2022

#### **POSTA KENYA**

Kakamega, Kenya ICT Support - Attaché May 2018 – Aug 2018

# **SKILLS**

- Database
- Programming
- Networking
- Website
- Microsoft Office
- Computer skills
- Customer service
- Helpdesk Support
- Teamwork
- Computer Hardware & Software

#### **PROJECTS & ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Attained subject mean grade of A plain (12 points) with 16 and 10 KCSE candidates class of 2021 and 2020 respectively.
- Developed two database management systems (Ms Access/Sal):
  - ◆ Movers Transport System (2021)
  - ◆ Fedha Youth Group System (2020)
- Developed Microsoft Excel Exams Analysis System (2021)
- Developed Java and MySQL-Db project Remote Health Alert & Monitoring System (2019)

RESUME WASHINGTONE